http://www.grimfells.net/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
You are here:
Home
Privacy Policy
The Shire-March of Grimfells, is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those businesses and/or individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with The Shire-March of Grimfells of your commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to grimfells.net and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of www.grimfells.net you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.
Collection of Information
This website collects various types of information, such as:
Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address and email address.
Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use personal/business information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this site.
It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.
Use of Information Collected
The Shire-March of Grimfells. may collect and may make use of the personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the product/services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from www.grimfells.net. The Shire-March of Grimfells. may also be in contact with you regarding completed surveys and/or questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future products/services that may be offered.
The Shire-March of Grimfells. does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.
The Shire-March of Grimfells. may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or id required in an effort to:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon The Shire-March of Grimfells. and/or our website;
Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of The Shire-March of Grimfells.; and
Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of
and/or the general public.
Children Under Age of 13
The Shire-March of Grimfells. does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.
Security
The Shire-March of Grimfells. shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal and/or business information under our control.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
The Shire-March of Grimfells. reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy. And as such we will post those changes to our website homepage at www.grimfells.net, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time The Shire-March of Grimfells. decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user and or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email:
The Shire-March of Grimfells covers most of the Northwest Arkansas 727XX zip code (from north to Bella Vista south almost to Fort Smith, west to Siloam Springs, and east to Harrison). Grimfells is but a small group which is part of a much larger kingdom, the Kingdom of Calontir. Calontir covers most of Kansas, Nebraska, Iowa, and Missouri, as well as North-West Arkansas.
Statement of Ownership
This is the recognized web site for the The Shire-March of Grimfells of the Society for Creative Anachronism, Inc. and is maintained by Wilhelm von Brandt. This site may contain electronic versions of the group’s governing documents. Any discrepancies between the electronic version of any information on this site and the printed version that is available from the originating office will be decided in favor of the printed version. For information on using photographs, articles, or artwork from this web site, please contact the Webminister at . He or she will assist you in contacting the original creator of the piece. Please respect the legal rights of our contributors.
Quick Links
Shire NewsSociety for Creative AnachronismKingdom of CalontirSCA MembershipOrder of PrecedenceSitemapPrivacy Policy
HomeGet StartedArts & SciencesMarshallateSCA Marshal's HandbookFighter Authorization ListWar ManualBlood Of Hero's RulesHeraldry CalendarGear Suppliers Contact
